复习练习 9-1：Mind Your Vees。下面开始段落。
Review exercise 9-1, mind your V's. Peter picked a peck of pickled peppers. It's
important to provide perfect principles for young people. Hopscotch, lollipops,
hula hoops, and popsicles keep a little nipper happy.
Laptop computers put payroll, payables, and spreadsheets at our fingertips.
It's impossible to predict population patterns. Betty bought a bit of better
butter. Ben believes Bill broke Bob's box. Billions of bagels are being baked in
Brooklyn. Babies babble and blow bubbles. Bananas come from Cuba. What were the
women doing in the woods? How would I know? When was Willie's worst weekend? Why
would we wear warm wool? Where were we when we woke up?
Fred forgot to fry fish on Friday. Few friends failed a fight. Freedom fighters
fight for freedom. Only a fool feeds fugu to friends. Feel free to laugh if it's
funny. It's evident that Vera was very valuable. Cliff Claven was available for
every version. The Navy revoked his visa for obvious reasons. Beavers give the
environment very valuable dams. Caves leave me cold, but I love to dive.